Finding Aid for the Dewey Daane Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- Top of Bookcase #2
  - Old Christmas Cards and Envelopes Unused Cassette- Lee Davis (both sides)
  - Business Card File
  - Stack of Old Sovran Bank Letterhead- JDD Equitable Securities Materials
    - Voorhies Bio
    - Other Assistants
    - Loose Notes
    - Equitable Newspaper Clippings (from Microfilm)
    - Loose Notes
    - Mark Riley
    - Equitable Securities Interview- Tom Hudson, 6/3/92
    - Draft #1 Nov 1997 Chapter 2- Equitable Securities
    - Loose Notes
    - Seminar on Monetary and Fiscal Policy- Tentative Speaker Schedule Spring 1995
  - Envelope with Notes and Cards (Top Right Credenza Drawer)
  - File- Misc. Materials
  - Expandable File- Snoden Village Association, L.P. (A Jacques Miller Investment)
- Bookcase #2 Shelf #1
  - Binder—Minute Book International Policy Committee- April 17, 1980- March 31, 1983 Binder—IPC Minutes Book, April 20, 1987- January 25, 1988
  - Binder—DRI Forecast
  - Binder—Fareast Trip Itinerary
  - Binder—Multinational Division- Three Year Plan, 1985-1987
  - Binder—Recommendation and Introduction Commerce Trading Corp-, Oct 1984
  - Binder—IPC Minutes, January 19, 1987- March 31, 1986
  - Binder—Three Year Plan – Unrevised
  - Binder—IMF/World Bank Meetings-, DC 1983 and 1984
  - Binder—1989- Financial Markets report- Sovran
  - Binder—1990- Blue Chip Market Indicator
  - Binder—IPC Minutes, January 21, 1986- October 18, 19813
  - Binder—NFA Manual
  - Binder—TVB- Organization and Senior Management Profiles
  - Binder—FRB- Kansas City- “Monetary Policy Issues in the 1990’s” KC Federal Symposium- Jackson Hole, Wyoming, 8/30-9/1/89
  - Binder—Whittaker Legal Dept Memo-, 11/29/88
- Bookcase #2 Shelf #2
  - Library of Southern Literature- Compiled under the Direct Supervision of Southern Men of Letters Vol. I-Vol. XVII- Martin and Hoyt Co., 1909
  - Book of the Thames: From Its Rise to Its Fall by Mr. And Mrs. S.C. Hall- Virtue and Co.-, 1880
- Top of Bookcase #3
  - 5 Large Envelopes with labels suggesting it is the contents of desk—very misc. materials: correspondence, notes, cards, business cards, receipts, etc.
- Bookcase #3 Shelf #1
  - America- Great Crises in Our History Told by Its Makers- A Library of Original Sources Vol. 1-12- Issued by Americanization Department VFW of US, 1925
  - Abraham Lincoln A History Vol. 1-10- John G. Nosegay and John Hay- the Century Co., 1890
- Bookcase #3 Shelf #2
  - One Man in His Time by Jack T. Conn ed by Odie B. Faulk Oklahoma Heritage Association, 1979
  - (Inscribed)
  - The Statesman’s Manual-Containing the President’s Messages- Inaugural, Annual, and Special from, 1789-
    - with their Memoirs and Histories of their Administrations. Compiled by Edwin Williams Vol.1-3 1854 [all three rebound], 1851
  - Ben Jonson L’Homme et L’Oevre 1572-1637—Maurice Castelain, 1907
  - Tennessee the Volunteer State, 1769-1923
  - The Century- Illustrated Monthly Magazine May 1893 to October 1893 Vol. XLVI
  - The Century- Illustrated Monthly Magazine May 1910 to, October 1910
  - The Book Wars- James Atlas, 1990
  - How to Make Love to Your Money- Mark Segall and Margaret Tobin, 1982
  - Fodor’s- Eastern Europe, 1983
  - Narodni Divadlo- Panorama Praha
  - Brasil Exparta- Texto de Antonio Olinto
  - Majesty and Wilderness Works by Carl Bungius
  - The Painful Prescription- Rational Hospital Care- Henry J. Aaron and William B. Schwartz- Brookings Institute, 1984
  - National Health Care in Great Britain: Lessons for the USA- John C. Goodman 1980 Summit at the Madison by Marshall B. Coyne
  - Richmond—Community Leadership
  - Antiques—The Diplomatic Reception Rooms- US Dept. of State
  - J.N. Bartfield Art Galleries, Inc.
  - Royal Canadian Air Force Exercise Plans for Physical Fitness
  - Portugal - A Bird’s Eye View
  - Tourist in Copenhagen
  - America Lawn Bowler’s Guide- Harvey C. Maxwell 1975 edition
  - Austria and Switzerland
  - This is Memphis
  - El Paisaje Barroco de Mexico
  - Mister Potter and His Bank—Jesse Hill Ford
  - Southvest LBO Fund, L.P.- Gen Cap America, Inc.
  - BIS 53rd Annual Report, June 13, 1983
  - Controlling Money- The Federal Reserve and Its Critics- Ralph C. Bryant 1962- France